Hello, English learners.
你好，英语学习者。
Welcome back to EnglishPod.
欢迎回到EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我叫Marco。
And my name is Kathryn.
我叫Kathryn。
And today Marco and I get to share with you the thrilling conclusion to the, well, very
今天Marco和我要和大家分享这个系列的激动人心的结局，嗯，我必须说，
popular I must say, series.
这个系列非常受欢迎。
I'm sorry, I love you.
对不起，我爱你。
That's right.
没错。
Today is the finale, the final episode, episode 10.
今天是结局，最后一集，第10集。
This is where it all ends.
一切都在这里结束。
So what do you think is going to happen?
那你觉得会发生什么？
If I guess, you're just going to get angry at me because I actually know how it ends.
如果我猜，你只会生我的气，因为我其实知道结局。
But let's just say I hope that it ends well for our protagonists.
但我就说我希望我们的主角能有个好结局。
There was a lot of controversy around it because, you know, I wanted to know if people wanted
关于这个有很多争议，因为，你知道，我想知道人们是想要
a happy ending, a sad ending, unexpected.
一个快乐的结局，一个悲伤的结局，还是意想不到的。
I guess everyone wants a happy ending, right?
我想每个人都想要一个快乐的结局，对吧？
Absolutely.
当然。
So we're going to, well, keep our fingers crossed for Steven and Veronica and check
所以我们要为Steven和Veronica祈祷，然后
out this dialogue one time.
一起看看这段对话。
Steven, good to see you, brother.
Steven，见到你真好，兄弟。
How are you?
你怎么样？
How was your trip?
你的旅行怎么样？
It was fine.
挺好的。
I've been better, but it's great to be home.
我状态不是最好，但回家真好。
I've missed you all.
我想你们所有人。
How's mom?
妈妈怎么样？
She's great.
她很好。
All she ever does is talk about you, her little boy that went to the United States.
她整天就念叨你，她那个去了美国的小儿子。
You're her pride and joy.
你是她的骄傲和快乐。
You know that, right?
你知道的，对吧？
I can't wait to see her.
我等不及要见她了。
You?
你呢？
What's new with you?
你有什么新鲜事？
Well, Nisha and I are expecting.
嗯，Nisha和我有喜了。
You'll have another nephew or niece soon.
你很快又要多一个侄子或侄女了。
That's great.
太好了。
Wow.
哇。
Congrats.
恭喜。
You two are great together, you know?
你们俩在一起很配，你知道吗？
You have such a beautiful family.
你有一个这么美好的家庭。
I hope that one day I can have that.
我希望有一天我也能拥有那样的生活。
Of course, man.
当然，兄弟。
Come on.
别这样。
I mean, everything was set here for you to marry Shalini.
我是说，这里一切都安排好了让你娶Shalini。
You know, she's still pining after you.
你知道，她还在为你憔悴。
I don't think she'll ever get over you.
我觉得她永远忘不了你。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
I hardly knew her.
我几乎不认识她。
How could she be in love with me?
她怎么会爱上我？
I couldn't go through with it, even though she's a great woman.
我做不到，尽管她是个好女人。
No, I left my heart in the United States.
不，我的心留在了美国。
I just hope Veronica is happy.
我只希望Veronica幸福。
Get over it.
忘了吧。
You're home now.
你现在回家了。
Everyone here thinks so highly of you.
这里每个人都对你评价很高。
There'll be girls throwing themselves at you.
会有女孩主动投怀送抱的。
You can marry anyone you want.
你可以娶任何你想娶的人。
I don't want to marry anyone.
我不想娶任何人。
I want to marry her.
我想娶她。
Don't you understand?
你不明白吗？
You are incorrigible.
你真是无可救药。
Steven!
Steven！
My baby!
我的宝贝！
How are you?
你好吗？
I miss you so much!
我好想你！
Hey, Mom.
嘿，妈妈。
Great to see you.
很高兴见到你。
You look so thin!
你看起来好瘦！
Didn't those Americans feed you?
那些美国人没给你饭吃吗？
Come, come.
来，来。
Let's have some Thai.
我们吃点泰国菜。
By the way, there is a girl here waiting for you.
顺便说一句，这里有个女孩在等你。
Hi, Steven.
嗨，Steven。
Veronica, how did you get here?
Veronica，你怎么到这里来的？
How do you know where I live?
你怎么知道我住哪里？
I waited for you at the airport, but you never showed.
我在机场等你，但你一直没出现。
I also have some little secrets that I haven't told you about, but we can discuss that later.
我还有一些小秘密没告诉你，不过我们可以晚点再谈。
I realized that I was just scared.
我意识到我只是害怕。
Scared of how much I love you and of the commitment that marriage requires.
害怕我有多爱你，害怕婚姻需要的承诺。
I'm here now.
我现在来了。
Now there's something I want to ask you.
现在我有件事想问你。
Steven, will you marry me?
Steven，你愿意娶我吗？
I now declare you husband and wife.
我现在宣布你们结为夫妻。
You may kiss the bride.
你可以亲吻新娘了。
All right, so they got married.
好了，所以他们结婚了。
You got married.
你结婚了。
We got married.
我们结婚了。
I got married.
我结婚了。
Wow, I should have called my mom.
哇，我该给我妈打个电话。
Not only did you get married, but you got married Bollywood style with music and everything
你不仅结婚了，而且是宝莱坞风格，有音乐和一切
nice.
美好的东西。
Those weddings are like four days long.
那些婚礼要持续四天。
I hope you enjoyed the finale of this story.
我希望你喜欢这个故事的结局。
Absolutely.
当然。
I was glad to see that it was a happy ending.
我很高兴看到这是一个快乐的结局。
I have to say if it had been a sad ending, I would have been a little bit disappointed
我不得不说，如果是个悲伤的结局，我会有点失望，
because well, Veronica and I...
因为，嗯，Veronica和我……
You get along.
你们相处得很好。
We get along.
我们相处得很好。
All right.
好了。
So apart from this happy ending and this happy finale that we had, we did look at a lot of
所以除了这个快乐的结局和我们这个快乐的结局之外，我们还看了很多
great words and phrases.
很棒的单词和短语。
So why don't we start now with language takeaway?
那我们为什么不从语言要点开始呢？
Language takeaway.
语言要点。
So the first couple of phrases I want to talk about here have to do with maybe catching
所以我想谈的前几个短语是关于
up and talking about family or gossip because we're talking to Stephen's Indian family who
叙旧和谈论家庭或八卦，因为我们正在和Stephen的印度家人交谈，他
hasn't seen for a long, long time.
很久很久没见到他们了。
The first thing he's talking to his brother about his brother and his wife.
他首先和他哥哥谈论他哥哥和他的妻子。
So Gulam and Nisha are expecting, we find out.
所以我们发现Gulam和Nisha有喜了。
Right, they're expecting.
对，他们有喜了。
So if Gulam and Nisha are expecting, what does that mean exactly?
所以如果Gulam和Nisha有喜了，那到底是什么意思？
They're expecting a letter.
他们在等一封信。
Expecting a baby maybe?
也许是在等一个宝宝？
Aha, yeah.
啊哈，是的。
So here we go.
所以就是这样。
So I'm expecting is a very common English way of saying I'm going to have a baby.
所以“I'm expecting”是一种很常见的英语说法，意思是我要生孩子了。
I'm pregnant.
我怀孕了。
All right.
好的。
So don't get this confused.
所以不要搞混了。
If somebody says, oh, well, I'm expecting, you don't have to say expecting what?
如果有人说，哦，嗯，我有喜了，你不需要问有喜什么？
Exactly.
没错。
When it's only expecting, when it's not a thing afterwards, I'm expecting means I'm
当只说“有喜了”，后面没有具体东西时，“我有喜了”意思是
pregnant or she's expecting.
我怀孕了或者她有喜了。
She's going to have a baby.
她要生孩子了。
So they are expecting a baby or they're expecting.
所以他们有喜了或者他们有喜了。
And they were talking about, well, Stephen, he was supposed to get married in India and
他们还在谈论，嗯，Stephen，他本来应该在印度结婚，
his brother said a very interesting, where he said, well, these girls are still, this
他哥哥说了一句很有趣的话，他说，嗯，这些女孩还在，这个
girl is still pining over you.
女孩还在为你憔悴。
So the Shalini, some girl that Stephen used to know when he was living in India, she's
所以Shalini，Stephen在印度时认识的一个女孩，她
pining after you.
在为你憔悴。
Well, pine has many different meanings in English.
嗯，“pine”在英语中有很多不同的意思。
But in this sense, we're talking about having a crush on or being in love with.
但在这个意义上，我们说的是迷恋或爱上。
And also it's a way of saying that you are, that you desire, you yearn for this person
而且这也是一种说法，表示你非常非常渴望、思念这个人，
very, very much.
非常非常。
But that you don't have them.
但你得不到他们。
Right.
对。
You don't have them.
你得不到他们。
You want them.
你想要他们。
So you're pining over this person.
所以你在为这个人憔悴。
Now, can you pine over an object?
现在，你能为一件物品憔悴吗？
No.
不能。
Usually it's maybe related to love or to a person, right?
通常这可能与爱情或一个人有关，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
So she, she stands by the door every day waiting the letter that doesn't come.
所以她每天站在门口等那封不来的信。
She's pining away for her dear love, Thomas or whatever.
她为她亲爱的爱人Thomas或谁而憔悴。
And you know what I read recently is that people can get addicted to pining.
你知道吗，我最近读到人们可能会对憔悴上瘾。
Really?
真的吗？
Yeah.
是的。
So maybe you can pine after a person not because you miss them or you want to, but you kind
所以你可能为一个人憔悴，不是因为你想念他们或你想要，而是你有点
of grow accustomed to it and you become addicted to this pain that's kind of pleasurable.
习惯了，你对这种有点愉悦的痛苦上瘾了。
There is a way to describe this.
有一种方式可以描述这个。
It's called Petrarchan love.
它叫做彼特拉克式爱情。
Well, it's this kind of traditional idea in poetry where you have a love that's never
嗯，这是诗歌中一种传统的观念，你有一种从未
consummated, that's never filled.
圆满、从未满足的爱情。
You never get to be with the person that you love, that you desire.
你永远无法和你爱、你渴望的人在一起。
And so it's a way, yeah, it's a way of distinguishing the two different kinds of love.
所以这是一种，是的，这是一种区分两种不同爱情的方式。
Some where you're with the person and the other where you always want them, but you
一种是你和那个人在一起，另一种是你总是想要他们，但你
can never have them.
永远得不到他们。
Well, hopefully none of our listeners are pining over anyone or, or get to experience
嗯，希望我们的听众中没有人在为任何人憔悴，或者经历
that, huh?
那种事，对吧？
Exactly.
没错。
But if you do pine away or you pine after someone, you have to hope that one day you'll
但如果你在憔悴或为某人憔悴，你必须希望有一天你会
get over that person.
忘记那个人。
Yeah, you have to get over it.
是的，你必须放下。
And that's what his brother says, hey, get over it.
这就是他哥哥说的，嘿，放下吧。
I don't think she'll ever get over you.
我觉得她永远忘不了你。
So what does it mean when you're supposed to get over someone?
那么当你应该忘记某人时，这意味着什么？
Okay, this is a good question because, you know, we're talking here not about actually
好的，这是个好问题，因为，你知道，我们这里说的不是真的
getting up on top of a fence or a wall.
爬过栅栏或墙。
We're talking about emotions.
我们说的是情感。
So getting over someone, so I have to get over him means that I have to stop feeling
所以忘记某人，所以我必须忘记他，意思是我必须停止
so sad about what, what happened, right?
为发生的事情感到难过，对吧？
Because usually you say this when someone's sad or angry.
因为通常当某人难过或生气时你会这么说。
And also it kind of means that you have to forget or let that person go, you know, like
而且这也意味着你必须忘记或放手那个人，你知道，就像
get over it.
放下吧。
We're going to move on here to the last word in today's language takeaway, which is incorrigible.
我们要继续讲今天语言要点的最后一个词，那就是“incorrigible”。
Okay, an incorrigible person.
好的，一个无可救药的人。
Alright, incorrigible.
好的，无可救药。
What could this mean?
这可能是什么意思？
Well, let's look at the sentence where we find it.
嗯，让我们看看我们找到它的句子。
You are incorrigible.
你真是无可救药。
Gulam says this to Stephen.
Gulam对Stephen这么说。
Right.
对。
So it's an adjective and basically it means that you have no correction of some sort.
所以这是一个形容词，基本上意思是你在某种程度上无法被纠正。
Well, there's an argument between Stephen and Gulam.
嗯，Stephen和Gulam之间有一场争论。
So they're brothers.
所以他们是兄弟。
And Stephen says, I don't want to get married.
Stephen说，我不想结婚。
I don't want to marry her.
我不想娶她。
He's complaining and his brother says, you are incorrigible.
他在抱怨，他哥哥说，你真是无可救药。
You just won't stop.
你就是停不下来。
So someone's feelings, their emotions, their ideas about something, they just can't be
所以某人的感受、情绪、对某事的想法，就是无法被
changed or altered.
改变或改变。
They're fixed.
他们是固定的。
You know, this guy, he's like, I'm not going to get married.
你知道，这家伙，他就像，我不会结婚。
And his brother says, you're incorrigible.
他哥哥说，你真是无可救药。
I just can't change your mind.
我就是无法改变你的想法。
It's kind of like being stubborn.
这有点像固执。
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
是的，是的，没错。
And we hear this phrase a lot together.
我们经常一起听到这个短语。
So you're incorrigible.
所以你是无可救药了。
So this is often just kind of a, it's not an insult, but it's a way for us to kind of
所以这通常只是一种，不是侮辱，而是我们用来
be sarcastic or to make fun of someone.
讽刺或取笑别人的方式。
You're incorrigible, Marco.
你真是无可救药，马可。
Usually you say it when you're loud, you know, you're being nice.
通常你说这话时，是因为你声音很大，但你其实是在表现友好。
Okay, cool.
好的，酷。
So five great words in language takeaway today.
所以今天语言学习环节有五个很棒的词。
And well, before we move on and listen to the dialogue again, why don't we take a look
在我们继续听对话之前，不如先看看
at Fluency Builder?
流利度提升环节？
Fluency Builder.
流利度提升。
All right.
好的。
So this phrase is something that parents often use and grandparents as well, because obviously
所以这个短语是父母和祖父母经常用的，因为显然
parents and grandparents, they're very proud of their children, their grandchildren.
父母和祖父母，他们为自己的孩子、孙子感到非常自豪。
So they describe something as being their pride and joy.
所以他们把某样东西描述为他们的骄傲和喜悦。
My pride and joy.
我的骄傲和喜悦。
So it's usually a person that's your pride and joy.
所以通常是一个人是你骄傲和喜悦的对象。
It could be a thing too.
也可能是一个东西。
It could be a thing.
His Porsche Boxster is his pride and joy.
他的保时捷Boxster是他的骄傲和喜悦。
He goes out every morning and he washes it.
他每天早上都出去洗车。
He changes the oil, he checks the gas, checks the tires.
他换机油，检查汽油，检查轮胎。
So it's his pride and joy.
所以那是他的骄傲和喜悦。
All right.
好的。
It's his most valued possession.
这是他最珍视的财产。
So it always goes together, right?
所以它总是连在一起用，对吧？
My pride and joy.
我的骄傲和喜悦。
Pride and joy.
骄傲和喜悦。
Yeah.
是的。
Just think of it as a phrase, pride and joy.
就把它当成一个短语，骄傲和喜悦。
All right.
好的。
So I'm my mother's pride and joy.
所以我是我妈妈的骄傲和喜悦。
I think you are.
我觉得你是。
All right.
好的。
So you don't know my mom.
所以你不认识我妈妈。
All right.
好的。
So somebody's pride and joy.
所以某人的骄傲和喜悦。
So now another phrase that we took a look at, and it's a way of making conversation,
现在我们来看另一个短语，这是一种聊天的方式，
especially with a person that you haven't seen in a while.
尤其是和很久没见的人。
He said, Hey, what's new with you?
他说，嘿，你最近有什么新鲜事？
What's new with you?
你最近有什么新鲜事？
All right.
好的。
So this might sound a little strange because normally we say, how have you been?
这听起来可能有点奇怪，因为我们通常说，你最近怎么样？
It's been a long time.
好久不见了。
How are you?
你好吗？
But this is like, you know, it's a fluency builder phrase.
但这就像，你知道，这是一个流利度提升短语。
So it's very colloquial, it's very spoken language.
所以它非常口语化，是非常地道的口语。
This you hear often between friends or family members.
你经常在朋友或家人之间听到这个。
Hey, Marco, what's new with you?
嘿，马可，你最近有什么新鲜事？
So how do you, I would answer this by saying, oh, well, not much.
那我该怎么回答呢？我会说，哦，没什么。
Or I just bought a new house.
或者我刚买了新房子。
So basically you're asking for news from a person.
所以基本上你是在问别人有什么新消息。
I haven't seen you in a long time.
我好久没见你了。
You look, you look happy and healthy.
你看起来，你看起来开心又健康。
So what's new with you?
所以你最近有什么新鲜事？
Oh, I got married.
哦，我结婚了。
I got a new car.
我买了新车。
These things that you can say, these are changes in my life.
这些你可以说，这些是我生活中的变化。
All right.
好的。
And usually after somebody asks you, what's new with you?
通常别人问你“你最近有什么新鲜事？”之后，
You say something and then you usually would follow up and ask that person as well, right?
你说点什么，然后通常也会回问那个人，对吧？
What's new and what's new with you?
有什么新鲜事？你最近有什么新鲜事？
Exactly.
没错。
So, you know, I got a new house, got a new job.
所以，你知道，我买了新房子，找了新工作。
What's new with you?
你最近有什么新鲜事？
Yeah.
是的。
Or what about you?
或者你呢？
What about you?
你呢？
So it's a nice, very relaxed, informal way of asking someone for news in their life.
所以这是一个很好、非常轻松、非正式的方式来询问别人生活中的新消息。
Perfect.
完美。
All right.
好的。
What's new with you?
你最近有什么新鲜事？
What else?
还有什么？
Now, he was supposed to get married, right?
现在，他本来要结婚的，对吧？
Right.
对。
So this is news.
所以这是新闻。
He was supposed to get married.
他本来要结婚的。
He didn't get married.
他没结婚。
What's going on?
怎么回事？
His brother, his mother, they all want to know what's going on.
他哥哥，他妈妈，他们都想知道怎么回事。
And we find out that wedding, that girl, he just couldn't go through with it.
然后我们发现婚礼，那个女孩，他就是没法坚持到底。
So I can't, I couldn't go through with it.
所以我不能，我无法坚持到底。
Okay.
好的。
This past tense.
这是过去时。
So he's saying, before I came to India with this girl, I couldn't go through with it.
所以他在说，在我和这个女孩来印度之前，我无法坚持到底。
So present would be, I can't go through with it.
所以现在时是，我无法坚持到底。
And going through with what here?
这里坚持什么？
We've got it, this kind of magical, strange word, it.
我们遇到了这个有点神奇、奇怪的词，“它”。
What could this be?
这可能是什么？
So basically, what he's saying is that he couldn't complete or maybe finish something
所以基本上，他在说他无法完成或结束
that he started.
他开始的事情。
Right.
对。
So in this case, we're talking about a relationship.
所以在这种情况下，我们在谈论一段关系。
Or marriage.
或者婚姻。
Yeah, a relationship.
是的，一段关系。
So maybe we loved each other, but I couldn't go through with it.
所以也许我们彼此相爱，但我无法坚持到底。
I couldn't go to the finish line.
我无法走到终点。
Right.
对。
I couldn't get married.
我无法结婚。
You see that a lot when maybe in movies, two people are supposed to get married.
你经常在电影里看到这种情况，两个人本来要结婚。
They're at the altar, and all of a sudden the bride says, I can't, or she goes away
他们在祭坛前，突然新娘说，我不能，或者她哭着
crying.
走开了。
I can't go through with this.
我无法坚持这个。
Exactly.
没错。
So because she loves somebody else, so can't go through with it.
因为她爱别人，所以无法坚持到底。
Great.
太好了。
So really good phrase.
所以真是个好短语。
I can't go through with it.
我无法坚持到底。
He couldn't go through with it.
他无法坚持到底。
And we find out that, well, not such a bad thing.
然后我们发现，嗯，也不是什么坏事。
Steven, he's very popular in India.
史蒂文，他在印度很受欢迎。
The girls love him.
女孩们都喜欢他。
We've got a great phrase for describing having lots of girls who love you.
我们有一个很好的短语来形容有很多女孩喜欢你。
Right.
对。
He says there will be girls throwing themselves at you.
他说会有女孩们主动投怀送抱。
Literally?
字面意思吗？
Like, ow, that might hurt.
比如，哎哟，那可能会疼。
I can't imagine that.
我无法想象。
Like, just somebody throwing themselves at you?
就像，有人直接扑向你？
No, it's not literal.
不，不是字面意思。
It's basically saying girls are very interested in you.
它基本上是说女孩们对你很感兴趣。
Girls are so interested in you that they'll be chasing you almost.
女孩们对你非常感兴趣，几乎会追着你跑。
All right.
好的。
So many, many girls, they will follow you.
所以很多很多女孩，她们会跟着你。
They'll want to be in a relationship with you.
她们想和你谈恋爱。
They like you.
她们喜欢你。
So he's saying, listen, there are other girls.
所以他在说，听着，还有其他女孩。
Don't worry.
别担心。
Girls here, they love you.
这里的女孩，她们爱你。
And it doesn't only work with girls, right?
而且这不只适用于女孩，对吧？
I can say there'll be boys throwing themselves at you.
我可以说会有男孩们主动投怀送抱。
Right.
对。
So this is something we say about both genders, boys and girls.
所以这是我们用来形容男女双方的，男孩和女孩。
You could say, oh, God, all the boys were throwing themselves at her.
你可以说，哦，天哪，所有男孩都对她投怀送抱。
I'm so jealous.
我好嫉妒。
Right.
对。
But it's only basically in a loving way, right?
但这基本上只是以爱的方式，对吧？
It can't be anything else.
不能是别的。
Like somebody's chasing you for other reasons.
比如有人因为其他原因追你。
No, this is saying that they have crushes, they have feelings, they want to be romantic.
不，这是说他们暗恋你，有感情，想浪漫。
It's not a bad thing, but sometimes it's too much attention, so it can be kind of negative.
这不是坏事，但有时关注太多，所以可能有点负面。
Yeah.
是的。
All right.
好的。
Well, interesting phrases on Fluency Builder today.
嗯，今天流利度提升环节的短语很有趣。
I think it's time for us to listen to this dialogue for one last time.
我想是时候让我们最后再听一遍这段对话了。
Get up and dance.
站起来跳舞。
Yeah.
是的。
Get up and dance.
站起来跳舞。
Stephen, good to see you, brother.
斯蒂芬，很高兴见到你，兄弟。
How are you?
你好吗？
How was your trip?
你的旅行怎么样？
It was fine.
还行。
I've been better, but it's great to be home.
我本来可以更好，但回家真好。
I've missed you all.
我很想念你们。
How's mom?
妈妈怎么样？
She's great.
她很好。
All she ever does is talk about you, her little boy that went to United States.
她整天都在谈论你，她那个去了美国的小男孩。
You're her pride and joy.
你是她的骄傲和喜悦。
You know that, right?
你知道的，对吧？
I can't wait to see you.
我迫不及待想见你。
You?
你呢？
What's new with you?
你最近有什么新鲜事？
Well, Nisha and I are expecting.
嗯，妮莎和我有喜了。
You'll have another nephew or niece soon.
你很快又会多一个侄子或侄女。
That's great.
太好了。
Wow.
哇。
Congrats.
恭喜。
You two are great together, you know?
你们俩在一起很般配，你知道吗？
You have such a beautiful family.
你有一个这么美好的家庭。
I hope that one day I can have that.
我希望有一天我也能拥有。
Of course, man.
当然，兄弟。
Come on.
别这样。
I mean, everything was set here for you to marry Shalini.
我的意思是，这里一切都安排好了让你娶莎莉妮。
You know, she's still finding after you.
你知道，她还在追你。
I don't think she'll ever get over you.
我觉得她永远忘不了你。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
I hardly knew her.
我几乎不认识她。
How could she be in love with me?
她怎么会爱上我？
I couldn't go through with it even though she's a great woman.
我无法坚持到底，尽管她是个好女人。
No, I left my heart in the United States.
不，我把心留在了美国。
I just hope Veronica is happy.
我只希望维罗妮卡幸福。
Get over it.
放下吧。
You're home now.
你现在回家了。
Everyone here thinks so highly of you.
这里每个人都对你评价很高。
They'll be girls throwing themselves at you.
会有女孩们主动投怀送抱。
You can marry anyone you want.
你可以娶任何你想娶的人。
I don't want to marry anyone.
我不想娶任何人。
I want to marry her.
我想娶她。
Don't you understand?
你不明白吗？
You are incorrigible.
你真是无可救药。
Steven, my baby, how are you?
史蒂文，我的宝贝，你好吗？
I miss you so much.
我好想你。
Hey, mom.
嘿，妈妈。
Great to see you.
很高兴见到你。
You look so thin.
你看起来好瘦。
Didn't those Americans feed you?
那些美国人没给你饭吃吗？
Come, come.
来，来。
Let's have some Thai.
我们吃点泰国菜吧。
By the way, there is a girl here waiting for you.
顺便说一句，这里有个女孩在等你。
Hi, Steven.
嗨，史蒂文。
Veronica, how did you get here?
维罗妮卡，你是怎么到这儿来的？
How do you know where I live?
你怎么知道我住哪儿？
I waited for you at the airport, but you never showed.
我在机场等你，但你一直没出现。
I also have some little secrets that I haven't told you about, but we can discuss that later.
我还有一些小秘密没告诉你，不过我们可以晚点再谈。
I realized that I was just scared, scared of how much I love you and of the commitment
我意识到我只是害怕，害怕我有多爱你，也害怕婚姻带来的
that marriage requires.
承诺。
I'm here now.
我现在来了。
Now, there's something I want to ask you.
现在，我有件事想问你。
Steven, will you marry me?
史蒂文，你愿意娶我吗？
I'm sorry, I don't think I can.
对不起，我想我不能。
I don't know how to say it.
我不知道该怎么说。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Alright, so it's over.
好吧，那就这样结束了。
Sad, sad but sweet.
悲伤，悲伤但甜蜜。
Sad but sweet, huh?
悲伤但甜蜜，嗯？
Well, we went from them meeting casually by a bike accident.
嗯，我们从他们因自行车事故偶然相遇开始。
Yeah, we had nice music.
是啊，我们配了不错的音乐。
Then it turned out that she was angry, they kind of broke up, they got back together.
然后她生气了，他们有点分手了，又复合了。
He was being strained with all of these secret trips to save people.
他因为那些秘密救人行动而压力重重。
It was interesting.
挺有意思的。
We went a lot of different ways.
我们走了很多不同的路线。
She was pregnant, she wasn't really pregnant.
她怀孕了，其实没真怀孕。
The doctor was stalking her.
那个医生在跟踪她。
She had a stalker.
她有个跟踪狂。
He's in the secret service.
他是特勤局的。
It was an interesting ride.
这是一段有趣的旅程。
Very interesting.
非常有趣。
Well, now we need to think of a new drama, a new soap opera or novel.
嗯，现在我们需要想一个新的剧情，一部新的肥皂剧或小说。
So, we need your input.
所以，我们需要你的意见。
Maybe we should open it up.
也许我们应该开放讨论。
What did you like?
你喜欢什么？
What didn't you like?
你不喜欢什么？
And what kind of genre are you interested in?
你对哪种类型感兴趣？
Because you know, there's tons of different kinds of stories we could tell.
因为你知道，我们可以讲很多种不同的故事。
Right, maybe we can do something scary like a thriller or horror.
对，也许我们可以做点吓人的，比如惊悚片或恐怖片。
I'm a big fan of sci-fi.
我是科幻片的超级粉丝。
Or sci-fi, maybe we can do something sci-fi.
或者科幻片，也许我们可以做点科幻题材的。
Maybe we can do a comedy, something maybe like Friends, I don't know.
也许我们可以做喜剧，比如像《老友记》那样的，我也不确定。
That'd be kind of cute.
那会挺可爱的。
Yeah, it could be.
是啊，有可能。
All right, so listeners, why don't you give us your input?
好了，听众们，你们为什么不给我们提提意见呢？
We need your feedback.
我们需要你们的反馈。
Tell us what series you would like next, what type of series.
告诉我们你们接下来想要什么系列，什么类型的系列。
Maybe, like we said, drama, sci-fi, action, what would you like?
也许，就像我们说的，剧情片、科幻片、动作片，你们想要什么？
And please get in touch with us, leave comments and questions at our website, englishpod.com.
请与我们联系，在我们的网站 englishpod.com 上留言和提问。
We like to check those and answer you.
我们喜欢查看并回复你们。
So, yeah, get in touch with us and have a great day.
所以，嗯，联系我们吧，祝你们有美好的一天。
All right, we'll see you guys there.
好了，我们那儿见。
Bye.
拜拜。